Siva Kupparajulu

Java J2EE Developer

An Experienced Java J2EE Developer with five years five months of experience in designing, developing and implementing applications and solutions using range of technologies. Passionate to learn new technology and always trying to give my best for my organization's development and growth.

ssivak58@gmail.com 🔀

+91-7207287775

Bangalore

sivakupparajulu.github.io./

linkedin.com/in/siva-007 in

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Software Engineer

Manhattan Associates

01/2018 - Present

Banglaore

Supply Chain Product Based Company Achievements/Tasks

- Working on Labor Management product to enhance the efficiency of the Labor performance in the Warehouse.
 Technologies: Spring framework, Spring REST, Hibernate and Oracle DB, Javascript, jQuery, HTML, CSS.
- Developed multiple modules in the product and supported the product with multiple customers around the globe in Implementing.
- Designed and developed multiple customer level enhancements to make their business easy.
- Leading a small team with 4 members and helping them learn the product/technology.
- Honored with multiple awards and promotions in the span of 3years.

Associate Software Engineer

Wipro Limited

10/2015 - 01/2018 Banglaore

Achievements/Tasks

- Worked on Bluedart Revamp project in implementing the complete project with latest technologies like Spring Restful webservices, Spring MVC, Hibernate as a backend developer.
- Used content management tool 'Liferay' for overall website management.
- Worked on Tamil Nadu Treasury project to build their Internal website for maintaining grievance requests.
- Used multiple technologies like Spring MVC, Hibernate, Javascript, jQuery, HTML, CSS and worked as a end to end full stack devleoper.

CERTIFICATES

JAVA 7 Oracle Certified Associate (OCA) (05/2017 - Present)

EDUCATION

B Tech in Electronics and Communication Engineering

Siddartha Institute of Science and Technology

2011 - 2015

SKILLS



ORGANIZATIONS

Manhattan Associates (01/2020 - Present) Senior Software Engineer

Manhattan Associates (01/2018 - 01/2020) Software Engineer

Wipro Limited (10/2015 - 01/2018)

Associate Software Engineer

HONOR AWARDS

Talent Transformation Toppers Award (2016)
Wipro Limited

 This award was given to the toppers of the freshers who was trained in Java J2EE

Manhattan Spot Bonus (2018)

Manhattan Associates

• This award is given for the employees on spot when the employee achieves something.

Manhattan Spirit Award (2019)

Manhattan Associates

 This award is given directly by the CEO for the Best employee of the year and will be nominated by others in the company.

Manhattan Star of the Quarter (2020)

Manhattan Associates

 This award is given by the Internal department for the Best employee of the quarter.

Manhattan Spot Bonus (2020)

Manhattan Associates

 This award is given for the employees on spot when the employee achieves something.

LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Tamil

Full Professional Proficiency

Telugu

Full Professional Proficiency